Noël Riley Fitch Papers, 1858-2012 (bulk 1965-1995): Finding Aid
Manuscripts Division
- Series 2: Correspondence, 1970s-1990s; 6 boxes
  - Subseries 2A: General, undated; 4 boxes
    - Solano, Solita, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 24)
    - Speyer, Darthea, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 25)
    - Spender, Stephen, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 26)
    - Statlender, Allanah Harper, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 27)
    - Stechert-Hafner, Inc., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 28)
    - Steloff, Frances [Gotham Book Mart], dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 29)
    - Streets, Mary, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 30)
    - Strickland, Ruth, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 31)
    - Stoltzfus, Ben, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 32)
    - S. West Books, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 33)
    - Tate, Allen, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 34)
    - Thompson, Lee E., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 35)
    - Thomson, Virgil, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 36)
    - Valéry, Francois, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 37)
    - Van Meter, Jane, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 38)
    - Veitch, Priscilla, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 39)
    - Ward, Thomas W. Jr., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 40)
    - Watson, Sarah P., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 41)
    - Weld, John, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 42)
    - Wescott, Glenway, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 43)
    - Wickes, George, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 44)
    - Wilder, Thornton, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 45)
    - Wineapple, Brenda, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 46)
    - Wiser, William, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 47)
    - Interviews/Correspondence Lists, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 48)
    - Travel- addresses, timelines, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 49)
    - Reviews and Miscellaneous Material, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 50)
  - Subseries 2B: Additional Correspondence, undated; 1 box
    Consists of additional correspondence with individuals such as William Howarth, James T. P. Mortensen, and Rebecca West, as well as others.
    This subseries is organized alphabetically by correspondent's last name.
    - Burke, Carolyn Greenstein, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - Goldman, Arnold, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - Gontarski, S. E., dates not examined; 1 box
    - Grogan, David F., dates not examined; 1 box
    - Gugitzer, Gabrille, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Henderson, Archie, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Hooker, Joan F., dates not examined; 1 box
    - Howarth, William, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Kerns, Phyllis, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Levitas, Irving, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Marchi, Dudley, M., dates not examined; 1 box
    - Mortensen, James T. P., dates not examined; 1 box
    - Powell, M. S., dates not examined; 1 box
    - Quinn, Noël, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Roberts, George D., dates not examined; 1 box
    - Robinson, Janice S., dates not examined; 1 box
    - Rose, Marilyn Gaddis, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Rubenstein, William D., dates not examined; 1 box
    - Rueckert, William, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Schub, Louise Rypko, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Scott, Bonnie Kime, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Simon, Linda, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Swerdlow, [Allan?], dates not examined; 1 box
    - Tanner, Allen, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Trabant, Warren and Jean, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Trilling, Richard, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Urnov, D. M. (Dmitri Mikhailovich), dates not examined; 1 box
    - Vanistartt, Questin, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Wallace, Emily M., dates not examined; 1 box
    - West, Rebecca, dates not examined; 1 box
    - William Carlos Williams Review, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Williams, William E., dates not examined; 1 box
    - Wilson, Van C., dates not examined; 1 box
    - Wolff, Geoffrey, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Woolmer, J. Howard, dates not examined; 1 box
  - Subseries 2C: Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated; 1 box
    This subseries consists of fan mail and responses to Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation: A History of Literary Paris in the Twenties and Thirties.
    Not arranged according to any arrangement scheme.
    - Public and friends' reactions to Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation, dates not examined; 3 folders (Folder 5-7)
  - Subseries 2D: Richard McDougall Correspondence and Poetry, 1977-1997; 1 box
    This subseries consists of Fitch's correspondence with Richard McDougall (d.1998), the author of The Very Rich Hours of Adrienne Monnier(1996), and assorted poetry manuscripts by McDougall.
    This subseries is organized first by material type (correspondence and manuscripts), and then chronologically.
    - 1977-1981, 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - 1981-1982, 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - 1983-1986, 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - 1986-1997, 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - A Selection of Poems(thesis, Iowa, 1957), by Richard McDougall, TMs (copy), 111 pp., inscribed to NRF, 1989; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - "Recent Poems," TMs (copy), ca.120 pp., 1990; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Additional poetry, TMs, 1992-1993; 1 folder (Folder 7)
- Series 3: Audiotapes, 1960-1990; 1 box
  This series consists of interviews conducted by Fitch, primarily concerning Sylvia Beach, and one microfilm reel of extracts from Robert A. Hipkiss' dissertation.
  This series is organized first by material type (cassette tapes, reel-to-reel tape, and microfilm), and then alphabetically and chronologically.
  - Cassette Tapes, 1960-1990; 1 box
    - Baltrusaitis, Hélène, and Maurice Saillet (Paris), undated; 1 box
    - Beach, Sylvia / Mathews, Jackson, for the Kenyon Review(#1), winter, 1960; 1 box
    - Beach, Sylvia / Mathews, Jackson, for the Kenyon Review(#2), winter, 1960; 1 box
    - Benoist-Méchin, Jacques (Paris), 1969 June 10; 1 box
    - Bishop, Elizabeth, 1978 June 28; 1 box
    - Bryan, Mina (P.U.L.), 1978; 1 box
    - Cody, Morrill, 1978 July 17; 1 box
    - Dennis, Fred, 1977 July 11; 1 box
    - Dennis, Fred, 1977 November 25; 1 box
    - Dennis, Fred, 1978 October; 1 box
    - Dennis, Fred, 1980 November 8; 1 box
    - Dennis, Fred, 1981 January 20; 1 box
    - Dennis, Fred, 1981 March 2; 1 box
    - Dennis, Fred, 1982 July; 1 box
    - Dutch Walk Tour (re: Hemingway), 1990; 1 box
    - Eddy, Helen, 1978 May 27; 1 box
    - Eddy, Helen, 1978 December 23; 1 box
    - Ellmann, Richard, 1981 March 16; 1 box
    - Fournier, Madame, 1969; 1 box
    - Freund, Gisèle, 1969; 1 box
    - Henley, Jean, 1978 March 2; 1 box
    - Mathews, Marthiel, 1978 July 18; 1 box
    - Swerdlow, Irwin, 1970 December 19; 1 box
    - Valéry, François, 1978 June 20; 1 box
    - Veitch, Priscilla (#1), 1978 July 23; 1 box
    - Veitch, Priscilla (#2), 1978 July 23; 1 box
  - Reel-to-reel Tape, 1966 January 10; 1 box
    - "Sylvia Beach - (M______?)", 1966 January 10; 1 box
  - Microfilm, 1966; 1 box
    - Hipkiss, Robert A., 1935- Extracts from his dissertation, Univ. of Calif., "The Values of Expatriation for the Major American Novelists, 1914-1941", 1966; 1 box
- Series 4: Printed Works, 1963-1995; 1 box
  This series consists of published copies of books by Fitch, Sylvia Beach, and others.
  - Thorsons Publishing Group, New Books, March-August 1989, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    Catalog, Thorsons Publishing Group Limited, Wellingborough, ill., 144 pp.
  - Fitch, Noël Riley: Literary Cafés of Paris(Washington, D.C.: Starrhill Press, 1989), dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    Paperback, ill., 79 pp.
  - Fitch, Noël Riley: Walks in Hemingway's Paris: A Guide to Paris for the Literary Traveler(New York: St. Martin's Press, 1990), dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    Paperback, ill., 195 pp.
  - Fitch, Noël Riley: Hemingway in Paris: Parisian Walks for the Literary Traveller (Wellingborough, Northamponshire: Equation, Thorson Publishing Group, 1989), dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 4)
  - Wagner-Martin, Linda: Favored Strangers: Gertrude Stein and her Family(New Brunswick, N.J.: Rutgers University Press, 1995), dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    Spiral bound (preview galley?)
  - Sylvia Beach, 1887-1962(Paris, Mercure de France, 1963), dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    Includes homages for Beach by T. S. Eliot, Marianne Moore, Bryher, and others, inscribed to Noel Riley Fitch by Marthiel Mathews, paperback, 174 pp.
  - Jay, Karla and Glasgow, Joanne, editors: Lesbian Texts and Contexts. Radical Revisions(N.Y.: New York University Press, 1990), dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 7)
  - Beach, Sylvia: Shakespeare and Company: Ein Buchladen in Paris(München: Paul List Verlag, undated), German edition, paperback, 288 pp., dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 8)
  - Princeton University Library Chronicle, Vol. XXVIII, winter, 1967, number 2, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    Contains "The Last Adventures of Ulysses" by A. Walton Litz.
- Series 5: Sylvia Beach Papers, 1858-1964; 5 boxes
  This series consists of assorted papers by or relating to Sylvia Beach and includes selections of correspondence of Beach and various family members, a typescript with autograph corrections of Beach's Shakespeare and Company, a taped interview (1960), photographs, memorabilia, reviews, obituaries, letters to Holly Beach, and estate papers.
  Arranged by genre of material.
  - Letters by Sylvia Beach, 1898-1952; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    3 ALsS, 5 ACsS to her parents and sisters
  - Correspondence of various Beach family members and friends, 1858-1954; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    12 ALsS, 7 ACsS by J. H. Orbison, John Newton, Elisabeth Morris, Holly Beach, Sylvester Beach, Adrienne [Monnier], and others
  - Photograph Album: "Italian and Serbian Pictures, Holly Beach Dennis", 1917-1920; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    77 photos (10 pp.) of Sylvia and Holly Beach who both worked for the Red Cross in Paris, Belgrade and Florence during World War I
  - Business Records, 1923; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    Photocopies from PUL's "Sylvia Beach Collection"
  - Memorabilia, circa 1932-1949; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    Clippings, programs, cards, an issue of "California Arts and Architecture" with an article by Frederic Beach Dennis, etc.
  - Correspondence of SB with Harcourt, Brace and Co, 1955-1962; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    Photocopies (of both sides of the correspondence)
  - Ulysses in Paris(N.Y.: Harcourt, Brace, 1956), dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    15 pp. of revised proof pages for the front matter to this work, which was a privately printed selection from Beach's Shakespeare and Company
  - Shakespeare and Company(London: Faber and Faber, 1959), 1950-1960; 3 boxes
    - Autograph manuscript page from an early draft, with corrections, 1950s; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - 2 sets of revised galley proofs, [1959], dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Scrapbook of newspaper clippings of reviews, 1959-1960; 1 folder (Folder 10)
    - "Faber and Faber, Spring and Summer Books" catalog, 1960; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - Typescript drafts, with autograph corrections, removed from Fitch's research files for Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation, dates not examined; 12 folders (Folder 1-12)
    - Ttypescript drafts, with autograph corrections, removed from Fitch's research files for Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation, dates not examined; 4 folders (Folder 1-4)
  - Holly Beach Dennis Correspondence, 1917-1964; 1 box
    - Correspondence with family and the American Red Cross, 1917-1922; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Letters of condolence to Holly Beach on Sylvia Beach's death, and miscellaneous letters (removed from the scrapbook in box 20), 1962-1964; 1 box
      - A-B, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      - Becat, Rinette, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 7)
      - Bryher, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 8)
      - C-K, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 9)
      - L-M, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 10)
      - N-R, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 11)
      - Saillet, Maurice, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 12)
      - S-Z, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 13)
      - Unidentified, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 14)
  - Estate of Sylvia Beach, 1962 October-1965 November; 4 folders (Folder 1-4)
    Correspondence of Holly Beach Dennis with Greenbaum, Wolff and Ernst, Princeton University Library, and others
  - Scrapbook pages, circa 1917-1953; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    Five loose pages containing 24 photographs of Sylvia Beach, Beach family and friends, and 22 cards and memorabilia
  - Scrapbook, 1962; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    Newspaper clippings of French and American obituaries of Sylvia Beach
- Series 6: Additional Papers, 1976-2012; 18 boxes; 2 items
  Consists of additional papers related to Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation: A History of Literary Paris in the Twenties and Thirties as well as additional lectures, articles, book reviews, photographs, writings, correspondence, and other papers.
  - Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation, 1983; 12 boxes
    This subseries consists of research notes; printed matter; clippings; material related to publication, publicity, and reviews; and an incomplete manuscript draft of chapters 1-20 for Fitch's Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation: A History of Literary Paris in the Twenties and Thirties.
    - Research notes, printed matter, clippings, etc., dates not examined; 7 boxes
      Rughly arranged chronologically, in NRF's folders.
    - Miscellaneous files on publishers, publicity and reviews of the book, dates not examined; 1 box
    - Typed drafts (chapters 1-20), incomplete, various revisions, dates not examined; 4 boxes
  - Lectures, Articles, Book Reviews, and Miscellaneous, 1979-1998; 2 boxes
    This subseries consists of assorted lectures, articles, book reviews, and other miscellaneous writings by Fitch. Also included is a folder of correspondence related to a James Joyce Symposium.
    This subseries is organized alphabetically by title or subject, as appropriate.
    - Americans in Paris, 1900-1930, A Selected, Annotated Bibliography by William G. Bailey - book review, 1990; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - "Americans in Paris: Shakespeare and Company" - lecture, 1979; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - "The Elusive 'Seamless' Whole: A Biographer Treats (or Fails to Treat) Lesbianism" - essay, published as chapter 5 in Lesbian Texts and Contexts, Radical Revisions, edited by K. Jay and J. Glasgow, 1990; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - Ezra Pound in London and Paris, 1908-1925 by J. J. Wilhelm - book review, 1991; 1 folder (Folder 4)
    - Gay and Lesbian Literary Heritage, edited by Claude Summers - essays on Sylvia Beach and Anaïs Nin, 1995; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - "Djuna Barnes" article for American Writers Supplement, 1990; 2 folders (Folder 6-7)
    - Djuna by Phillip Herring and Nightwood by Djuna Barnes - book reviews, 1996; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - James Joyce Symposium - correspondence, 1988; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Modern Language Association - conference papers, 1979; 1 folder (Folder 10)
    - Modern Language Association - conference papers, 1984; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - Silence and Power: A Reevaluation of Djuna Barnes, edited by Mary Lynn Broe - book review, 1991; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - "Sylvia Beach" - article for American National Biography, 1996; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - "Sylvia Beach in Paris: the French Connection" - lecture, 1979; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - "This is Everybody's Life" - article, 1998; 1 folder (Folder 4)
  - Papers of Others, 1979; 1 box; 2 items
    This subseries consists of Lisa MacFarlane's thesis on Sylvia Beach, "For Who is Silvier."
    - MacFarlane, Lisa, 1979; 1 folder (Folder 5)
      - "For Who is Silvier" - Princeton University thesis on Sylvia Beach, 1979; 1 item
  - Additional Writings, 1988; 1 box
    This subseries consists of four lectures and unpublished papers by Fitch. For additional writings by Fitch, see also series I. Works.
    Arranged alphabetically by title.
    - "Gertrude Stein and Alice B. Toklas-Food: The Sacrament of Their Devotion", undated; 1 folder (Folder 1)
      TMs with revisions (Xerox), 18 pp., undated ANs and TNs, 36 pp.
    - "Paris in the Narrative Space of Joyce and Stephen Dedalus", undated; 1 folder (Folder 2)
      TMs with revisions, 17 pp.[includes maps (Xerox)], 1988 TMs with revisions, 14 pp. [includes maps (Xerox)], 1988 ANs and TNs, 10 pp. [includes maps (Xerox)]
    - "Sylvia" [screenplay for Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation: A History of Literary Paris in the Twenties and Thirties, undated; 1 folder (Folder 3)
      TMs with revisions (Xerox) and TMs with revisions (fragments), 10 pp.
    - "Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation in Paris" [speech delivered at The Mount, Lennox, Massachusetts], 1998; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      TMs with revisions, 12 pp.
  - Additional Correspondence, 1976-2002; 2 boxes
    This subseries consists of correspondence between Fitch and her literary agents, friends, and fans primarily relating to Fitch's books concerning Lost Generation authors. For additional correspondence, see also Series 2, Correspondence.
    This subseries is organized alphabetically by subject according to Fitch's original folder headings, where possible, or by last name of the correspondent.
    - [Unknown] [?], Jean, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - A-C General, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 6)
      Access Press
      Asselineau, R.
      Banta, Charles
      Beegel, Susan
      Benstock, Bernard
      Boorman, John
      Bryer, Jackson
      Carson, Tom
      Charles Scribner's Sons [see also Hemingway, Ernest (as subject)]
      Cook, Virginia
      Cousins, Judith
      Cox, Stephen
      Crocker, Charles, III
    - Allsup, James, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Areté: Forum for Thought, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Baker, Jean-Claude, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Benstock, Shari [see also Toklas, Alice B. (as subject)], dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 10)
    - Bessie, Dan, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - Boegeman, Margaret Byrd, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 12)
    - Broe, Mary Lynn, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 13)
    - Conover Carson, Anne, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 14)
    - Cousineau, Phil, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 15)
    - D-I General, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 16)
      de Vost, Nadine
      Edith Wharton Restoration [see The Mount]
      Faus, Colette
      Friedman, Susan
      Gerber, Anna
      Giroux, Robert
      Haight, Mary Ellen
      Henke, Suzette
      Herdin, Terry
      Herring, Phillip
      Ishkanian, Elinor
    - Duncan, Mary, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 17)
    - Grace, Sherrill, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 18)
    - The Harvester Press, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 19)
    - Hellier, Odile, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 20)
    - Hemingway, Ernest [as subject], dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 21)
      [?], George
      [?], Robin
      Boyle, Kay
      Charles Scribner's Sons [see also A-C General]
      Freund, Gisele
      Joyce, William L.
      Lewis, Robert W.
      Macmillan Publishing Company
      Peterson, Martin
      Phillips, Christopher
      Roger-Viollet
      Sanderson, Rena
      Thorsons Publishing Group
    - Holly, Marcia, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 22)
    - Jezebel Productions, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 23)
    - K-O General, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 24)
      Kurth, Peter
      Levine, Marilyn
      Lewis, R. W. B.
      Matn, Militte
      McFarland, Lisa
      McLendon, Ruth
      Munro, Evelyn
      Murat, Princess Pauline
      Overbeck, Lois
    - Lane, Gentry, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 25)
    - Lang Fuller, Christa, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 26)
    - Literary Cafés of Paris: Responses, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 27)
    - Litz, Walton, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 28)
    - Maddox, Brenda, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 1)
    - McBride, Margaret, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 2)
    - The Mount [Edith Wharton Restoration], dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 3)
    - P-W General, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 4)
      Potts, Bill
      Random House
      Reynolds, Michael
      Robertson, Robert
      Romine, Jennifer
      Scherman, David
      Schroeder, Carolyn
      Selth, Jefferson
      Stimpson, Catherine R.
      Temple University
      Toklas, Alice B. Toklas [as subject]
      Benstock, Shari [see also Benstock, Shari]
      Sabban, Françoise
      Wagner-Martin, Linda
      Wickens, George
      Wiser, Bill
    - Penguin Books, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 5)
    - Princeton University, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 6)
    - Roberts, John, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 7)
    - Rollyson, Carl, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 8)
    - Shelly Power Literary Agency, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 9)
    - Sherman, Ken, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 10)
    - Sylvia Beach and the Lost Generation: A History of Literary Paris in the Twenties and Thirties: Responses, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 11)
    - Sylvia Beach Hotel, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 12)
    - Thorsons Publishing Group [see also Hemingway, Ernest (as subject)], dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 13)
    - Walks in Hemingway's Paris: A Guide for the Literary Traveler: Responses, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 14)
    - Weld, Katy and John, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 15)
    - Wheelock, Martha, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 16)
    - Whitman, George, dates not examined; 1 folder (Folder 17)
  - Photograph, undated; 1 box
    A photograph by David E. Scherman of photographs hanging in Shakespeare and Company.
  - Voyage to Ithaca: William Carlos Williams in Paris, 1976-1980; 1 folder (Folder 18)
    Several typescript drafts of "Voyage to Ithaca," with hologgraph corrections, annotations, and additions by Fitch; and correspondence with Else Albrecht-Carrie, Donald Gallup, James Laughlin, Marilyn V. Schuler, Emily Wallace, and Mrs. William Carlos Williams, related to the above manuscript, which was published in the Princeton University Library Chronicle, XL (spring 1979): 193-214. AM 1996-01.
  - Additions, 1970s-2012; 1 box
    Additional correspondence, manuscripts, and photographs. AM 2011-94, 2013-78.
- 32101037506894 (Box 1)
- 32101037506902 (Box 2)
- 32101037506910 (Box 3)
- 32101037506928 (Box 4)
- 32101037506936 (Box 5)
- 32101037506944 (Box 6)
- 32101037506951 (Box 7)
- 32101037506969 (Box 8)
- 32101037506977 (Box 9)
- 32101037506985 (Box 10)
- 32101037506993 (Box 11)
- 32101037507009 (Box 12)
- 32101037507017 (Box 12A)
- 32101037507025 (Box 13)
- 32101037507033 (Box 14)
- 32101037507041 (Box 15)
- 32101037507058 (Box 16)
- 32101037507066 (Box 17)
- 32101037507074 (Box 18)
- 32101037507082 (Box 19)
- 32101037507090 (Box 20)
- 32101037507108 (Box 21)
- 32101037507116 (Box 22)
- 32101037507124 (Box 23)
- 32101037507132 (Box 24)
- 32101037507140 (Box 25)
- 32101037507157 (Box 26)
- 32101037507165 (Box 27)
- 32101037507173 (Box 28)
- 32101037507181 (Box 29)
- 32101037507199 (Box 30)
- 32101037507207 (Box 31)
- 32101037507215 (Box 32)
- 32101037507223 (Box 33)
- 32101037507231 (Box 34)
- 32101037507249 (Box 35)
- 32101037507256 (Box 36)
- 32101080519729 (Box 38)
- 32101038580898 (Box 37)